Hi, I'm Paula and this is a short video about
how BPlan DIY works.
Most business plans use hard to complete templates and separate complicated
spreadsheets. BPlan DIY builds your plan and your cash flow
forecast at the same time in five simple steps.
It's easy. We gather the information about your business and the market
opportunity and consider your ambition.
You can use AI to make suggestions and help you with how you're
going to achieve your goals. Finally,
you complete your cash flow forecast and see clearly how your business
will achieve success. When you're happy,
generate your business plan, which can be branded for your business and
downloaded to Word. Use your plan to apply for bank or investor
funding or to keep measuring your business success.
So get started today. Thanks for listening.